Enoch Chejieh

Software Engineer

enochchejieh@gmail.com +2348115911976 https://www.linkedin.com/in/enoch-chejieh-a39652155

SUMMARY

https://enochchejieh.netlify.app

Enoch Chejieh is a software engineer with 1+ year of experience ranging from frontend to backend technologies.

Experienced Frontend developer (VueJs, NuxtJs, ReactJs, HTML, and CSS) with high consideration for web accessibility.

He is passionate about open-source and also making the web more accessible to everyone, he enjoys writing articles, sharing his knowledge.

EDUCATION

BABCOCK UNIVERSITY, Ilishan-Remo, Nigeria

Bachelor of Science - BS, Computer Science (Technology) 2017 - 2021

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

• Vuels • Nuxtls

https://github.com/ECJ222

• ReactIs

• NodeJs

Lagos, Nigeria

- MongoDB
- GraphQL
- Strapi

• Technical Writing

• Test Driven
Development

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer | Acumen Digital (Lagos, Nigeria) | October 2020 - present

- Implemented frontend-related tasks using VueJS and NuxtJs based on user requirements from the product team.
- Designed interactive UI mockups based on user requirements.
- Improved performance and accessibility of user websites.
- Responsible for quality assurance of finished websites including testing and debugging of code.

Software Developer Intern | Kamusi Project International / USA | August 2018 - September 2018

• Designed UI features for a web e-learning platform.

enochchejieh@gmail.com 1 / 1